A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Hartford Institute for Geriatric Nursing and New York University, Nurses Improving Care for Healthsystem Elders (NICHE), Series 9 FA1721
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Hartford Institute for Geriatric Nursing and New York University, Nurses Improving Care for Healthsystem Elders (NICHE), 1997-2006; 9; 52.57 Cubic Feet
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 100527-100694 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 100527-100694 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 100695-100785 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 100695-100785 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 100695-100785 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 100695-100785 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 100695-100785 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 100786-100891 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 100786-100891 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 100786-100891 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 100786-100891 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 100786-100891 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 100892-100999 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 100892-100999 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 100892-100999 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 100892-100999 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 100892-100999 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 101001-101166 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 101001-101166 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 101001-101166 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 101001-101166 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 101001-101166 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 101167-101329 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 101167-101329 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 101167-101329 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 101167-101329 (Box 37)
  - Memorial, Illinois, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 101167-101329 (Box 37)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 21100-21210 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 21100-21210 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 21100-21210 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 21211-21360 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 21211-21360 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 21211-21360 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 21366-21537 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 21366-21537 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 21366-21537 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 21538-21620 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 21538-21620 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 21538-21620 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 21621-21725 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 21621-21725 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 21621-21725 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 21726-21818 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 21726-21818 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 21726-21818 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 21820-21911 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 21820-21911 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 21820-21911 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 21912-22034 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 21912-22034 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 21912-22034 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 22035-22219 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 22035-22219 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 22035-22219 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 22220-22347 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 22220-22347 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 22220-22347 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 22348-22412 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 22348-22412 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 22348-22412 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 22413-22505 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 22413-22505 (Box 38)
  - Mercy Oakland, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 22413-22505 (Box 38)
  - Metrowest Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 1201-1295 (Box 39)
  - Metrowest Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 1201-1295 (Box 39)
  - Metrowest Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 1201-1295 (Box 39)
  - Metrowest Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 1299-103166 (Box 39)
  - Metrowest Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 1299-103166 (Box 39)
  - Metrowest Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 1299-103166 (Box 39)
  - Metrowest Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 10317-10331 (Box 39)
  - Metrowest Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 10317-10331 (Box 39)
  - Metrowest Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 10317-10331 (Box 39)
  - Miami Valley Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D1, 112340-112954 (Box 39)
  - Miami Valley Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D1, 112955-113520 (Box 39)
  - Miami Valley Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D1, 113521-114115 (Box 39)
  - Miami Valley Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D1, 114116-115388 (Box 39)
  - Miami Valley Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 112340-112954 (Box 39)
  - Miami Valley Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 112955-113519 (Box 39)
  - Miami Valley Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 113520-114072 (Box 40)
  - Miami Valley Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 114073-115388 (Box 40)
  - Miami Valley Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3, 112340-112964 (Box 40)
  - Miami Valley Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3, 112958-113508 (Box 40)
  - Miami Valley Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3, 113510-114086 (Box 40)